{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React Updated",
      "description": "Updated: React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "Update React Router",
      "description": "Updated: React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "new deck",
      "description": "new deck description",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "How do you modify the state of a different React component?",
      "back": "Not at all! State is visible to the component only.",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "How do you pass data 'down' to a React child component?",
      "back": "As properties or props",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "New Card one Front",
      "back": "New Card one Back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "new card two front",
      "back": "new card two back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "new card 3 front",
      "back": "new card 3 back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "new card 4 front",
      "back": "new card 4 back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "new card 10 front",
      "back": "new card 10 back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "add front",
      "back": "add back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "new card front edit again",
      "back": "new card back edit again",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "new card front ",
      "back": "new card back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "new card front jan 6 edit",
      "back": "new card back jan 6 edit",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "new front add using cardform",
      "back": "new back add using cardform",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "new card front using form",
      "back": "new card back using form",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "new card front 4",
      "back": "new card back 4",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "new front",
      "back": "new back",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "new cart front Jan 9",
      "back": "new cart back Jan 9",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "new cart front garden",
      "back": "new cart back garden",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "new card 1 from",
      "back": "new card 1 back",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "new card 2 front",
      "back": "new card 2 back",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 24
    }
  ]
}